AMIT KUMAR Sr. Sales Executive

CONTACT

C

8368891838

amitsiradhna@gmail.com

命

618/7 Haiderpur, Shalimar Bagh Delhi-110088

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Business Administration.

> Mahatma Gandhi University 2011 - 2014

School Completed

NVN Boarding School, Jaipur 12th = 2008-2009

SMS Boarding school, Jaipur 10th = 2010 - 2011

SKILL

- Good listening and Observation.
- Good communication and relationships build.
- Fast build relationships.
- Decision making .
- Hard working.
- SALES SKILL.
- Time management.

LANGUAGE

- English
- Hindi

Career Objective

Add value to my career in the organization where i work smart and to emerge as a successful corporate through hard work with dedication, also want to be recognised as a top professional in a organisation.

Profile

5 years plus experience in sales and marketing of bathware product in building materials industry. Strong in market analysis for high business volume with ability to make a build relationships to customer for long business partnership. Good in problem solving and customer Handling

Experience

O Nov 2023 - Present WATERTEC (INDIA) PVT LTD.

SENIOR SALES EXECUTIVE

Working as a senior sales executive entire north delhi and west delhi, takeing care chanel sales devision dealers. Deals in polymer water taps, bathware product and accessories. Do efforts new market for new dealers and follow up to generate the new sales and build a good relationship every dealers for long term business and high volume sales.

Feb 2022 - Oct 2023 EVIC BATHWARE

Senior SALES EXECUTIVE

Responsibility of handling distributor and dealers entire north and west Delhi areas.Do the work of dealing in cp fittings items water taps, Bath ware product and accessories.Do efforts new market for new dealers and follow up to generate the new sales and build a good relationship every dealers for long term business and high volume sales. Posted as a senior position with 2 person team for Rajasthan location.

June 2018 - Feb 2022 HAZEL

Sales EXECUTIVE

Here I am work for Makes new dealers to achieve the assign target.Do efforts new market for new dealers and follow up to generate the new sales and build a good relationship every dealers for long term business and high volume sales. Promoted as a senior sales executive in 2019.

Sep 2017 - Apr 2018
ABBIE-IT-MART

SENIOR SERVICE ENGINEER

Here i am work as senior service engineer part of tech-support team to help to solved problem and a good service to our business partners. As a senior service executive responsibility tech support team and taking care of team problem solving and support. Here I do work after sales services advertising online platform.

JUNE 2016 - AUG 2017

M-SWIPE TECHNOLOGY PVT LTD

CUSTOMER SERVICE REPRESENTATIVE

As a Senior FSE and Trainer in Operation team. Here i am work POS Machine installation and operated working process.

Area Service head UP, HARYANA AND RAJASTHAN.

OCT 2014 - MAY 2016
 GSK PVT LTD

MARKETING AND SALES REPRESENTATIVE

Responsible work as a Marketing and Sales Representative.deal in pharma products and daily visit hospital, chemist, doctors and general shop in market